galtsgulchonline.com 2014-07-04

# Galt's Gulch - Privacy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To personalize your experience   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

To improve our website   
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

To improve customer service   
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

To process transactions 

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 

To send periodic emails 

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into 'My Account' and going to the 'Your Account Details' page. 

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://store.atlasshruggedmovie.com/shipping-returns/>

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/). 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 08/03/2012

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.galtsgulchonline.com/contact   
56 N. Haddon Avenue, 3rd Flr   
Haddonfield, NJ 08033   
USA   
admin@galtsgulchonline.com 

This policy is powered by Trust Guard [PCI compliance](http://www.trust-guard.com/PCI-Compliance-s/65.htm). 

You must be signed in to do that. Would you like to sign in now?

While we're very happy to have you in the Gulch and appreciate your wanting to fully engage, some things in the Gulch ( _e.g. voting, links in comments_ ) are a privilege, not a right. To get you up to speed as quickly as possible, we've provided two options for earning these privileges. 

  1. You must reach a Gulch score of 100. You can earn points in the Gulch by posting content, commenting, or by other members voting up your posts.
  2. You may upgrade to a Galt's Gulch **Producer** membership to immediately gain these privilege.

Your current Gulch score: ****
